> > Brian Holt: 现在我们要在这里写一些代码。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
now we're gonna write some code in here.
而不是我们的剧本我要说康斯特
Instead of our script tag,
I'm gonna say const.
应用程序。
App.
等于一个箭头函数。
Equals an arrow function.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 所以你们中的一些人可能被这个象形文字所迷思了。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So some of you might be
mystified by this hieroglyphic here.
这就是所谓的字体结扎。
This is what's called a font ligature.
所以我有个特别的字体来让它很美
So, I have a special font to make
it beautiful that I've installed
当我有一些彼此相邻的角色时，它将它们组合在一起。
that when I have certain characters that
are next to each other, it combines them.
很漂亮所以我才这么做
It's pretty, so that's why I do it.
它的认知开销也不如一个字符，而不是两个字符。
It also supposedly less cognitive overhead
parts one character instead of two.
Blah ， blah， blah.
Blah, blah, blah.
我这么做是因为我觉得它看起来不错
I do it because I think it looks nice.
所以如果我把空间放在这里，你会看到它实际上是在等号和
So if I put space here, you'll see
that it's actually in equal signs and
一个角度的支架但是如果你把它们放在一起的话
an angle bracket, but
if you put them together it's get that.
所以我要尽快给你展示我经常被问到的
So I'm just gonna show you very quickly
how to do that cuz I frequently get asked
我怎么才能得到这个
on how do I get that for myself.
我用的这个字体的名字叫 Dank Mono。
The name of this font that I'm
using is called Dank Mono.
我没说这就是它的名字
I didn't name it,
that's exactly what it's called.
在 Dank.sh，这些优秀的人实际上赞助了并置或
At Dank.sh, these wonderful people
actually sponsored concatenate or
我们的会议对他们大喊大叫
our conference so shout out to them.
这是一个 50 美元的字体为了现在的 40 磅
This is a $50 font for
the sake it's 40 pounds now,
大概是五十多块吧
which is I guess more than $50.
如果你愿意的话你可以得到这个
So you can get that if you want to.
你花了很多时间看字体
You spent a lot of time looking at font,
so
这可能是我无法从这件事中得到的教训
that might be something to consider I
get no kick back from this by the way.
我只是个粉丝
I'm just a fan.
但是如果你不想付钱
But, if you don't wanna pay for one,
还有一个叫 FILA 的代码是免费的
there's another one called
FIRA Code that is free.
>> Brian Holt: 这个很好的人已经为你做了这件事。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And this very nice
person has done that for you.
有办法安装它。
And there are ways to install it.
所以如何安装，你可以把它弄下来。
So how to install,
you can get that down here.
我把它关掉了是很容易做到的
I got it off which is
the easy way to do it.
因此，  将是另一个。
So, FiraCode would be the other one.
好的，一旦你安装了其中一个，你就会把它放进去
Okay, so once you have one of those
installed, the way that you put that into
VS 码是我要打开我的设置
VS code is, I'm gonna open my settings so,
preferences,
或者您可以使用命令逗号来命中命令，无论窗口是什么。
settings here, or you can hit command
comma, whatever that would be for windows.
好吧那你得换两件事情
Okay, so you have to change two things.
你必须改变的是你的战线
One of them you have to
change is your front.
在这里我第一次和菲拉法第二次
So here, I have Dank Mono first and
FiraCode second,
它就像一个 CSS 的权利，所以它会得到我能找到的第一个，好的。
it works just like a CSS right, so it'll
get the first one that I can find, okay.
然后你可以看到这里的编辑字体
And then you can see here
Editor Font Ligatures,
你也得让这一点
you have to enable that as well.
好，这样就可以让角色的实际结合了。
Right, so that'll allow the actual
combining of characters.
所以如果我回去了别救了
So if I go back to, don't save
在我的， >> Brian Holt:
over my,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So like
如果我现在就把它关掉，你可以看到我有这个箭头。
if I were to turn off ligatures right now,
you can see here that I have this arrow.
但如果我把它关掉， >> Brian Holt: 你会发现
But if I turned it off,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You'll see that it gets
又分开了
separated again.
那就好
So, cool.
这就是你的连接方式。
So that's how you enable ligatures.